oh
お
help
手 伝
I'll do it
い してく
Thank you very much.
れて ありがとう
Have you really never given a blow job?
ほんまにフェラーしたことない?
Yeah, that's right.
うん、 そうだね
Oh, it feels good.
おー気持ちいい
Let me know when you go home.
お家行くとき教えてよ
I think I'm going to go.
行っちゃいそう
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
I think I'm going to go.
行っちゃいそう
It's cute.
かわいいね
cute.
かわいい
I went.
行っちゃった
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
Wow.
うーわ
Super pink.
すーごいピンク
It's been a while since I've seen pink like this.
久々にこんなピンク見た
Guru-chan, are you weak?
グルちゃん、弱い?
Yeah.
うん
cute.
かわいい
It's too loud so I'm going to turn away?
うっさいからベカらんでちゃう?
face.
顔
Is it not okay at all?
全然オッケーくない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
I feel like I'm sweating.
汗がおる気もして
Yeah.
うん
vinegar
す
- Great?
ー ごい?
Let's move together.
一緒に動いてやるとね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Ah, nice.
あー いいね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
I end up falling behind.
後ろ巻きになっちゃう
Roll backwards?
後ろ巻き?
You can take it out once.
一回抜いていいよ
Roll it backwards.
後ろ巻きね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels really good.
めっちゃ気持ちいいんだね
copper?
どう?
amazing.
すごい
I feel good about myself.
自分の気持ちいいよ
feelings
気 持
Good.
ち いい
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
そうそう そう
Before?
前か
oh yeah
そうそう
yes.
そう
A little while ago.
もう ちょっと前
ah.
あー
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
Oh no.
あーダメだ
I think I'm going to go.
行っちゃいそう
Take a look.
ズボズボしてごらん
Ah, let's go.
あー行くぞ
Ah, go, go.
あー行く行く
I'm sleeping a lot.
めっちゃ寝てます
First time?
初めてした?
Yeah.
うん
Is that your first time?
ああいうの初めて?
Yeah.
うん
Can you move?
動ける?
a little bit.
ちょっと
So
そ
press this button
この ボタンを押して
please.
ください
Is it getting power?
パ ワー出てる?
expensive.
高い
Will the power come out?
パワー出ちゃう?
Power is coming out.
パ ワー出てる
It's going to rain.
降るんだよ
amazing.
すごい
What do you think about the long back?
後ろ背長ついて、どう?
a,
あ、
It looks super long.
超 押し長く見えるよ
Awesome.
すげー
My legs are really stretched out.
めっちゃ足伸んでる
Great, I'll stretch my legs.
すごい、足伸ばすよ
Tall, tall.
背長ついて、背長
How was it earlier?
さっきどうだった?
Have you ever moved like that?
あ んな動き方したことない?
do not have.
ない
Even now, my hips are still moving.
終わった後の腰が今も動いてる
Is it just called normally?
普通に呼ばれるだけ?
everytime.
いつも
I don't particularly move.
自分は特に動かない
Especially since I move around a lot.
自分は特にあんま動いてるから
It came out a little foamy.
ちょっと泡っぽいの出てきた
Bubble?
泡?
Bubbles have formed.
泡出来てきたよ
Bubbles.
泡泡
Actually, I really can do it.
ほんとはほんと出来るんだけどね
appear?
見える?
There are various keys.
色々とキーがあるね
good?
いい?
good.
いい
There are some nice colors.
いい色があるね
Which one feels better?
どっちが気持ちいい?
Which one?
どっち?
How many points to the left?
多分左?
This way?
こっち?
Yeah.
うん
Don't go out.
外出るな
That's a really cool face.
めっちゃそれん顔だよな
yes?
そう?
Oh no.
やば
Try spreading your legs.
足広げてみて
Nice to meet you.
よろしくね
Thank you very much.
ちょっとよろしく
So dead.
すごい死んだ
Looks like it'll live.
生きそう
Looks like it'll be alive.
生きそうだね
It feels kind of weird.
なんか変な感じ
It feels weird.
変な感じ
It feels so weird.
すごい 変な感じ
Yeah.
うん
stomach
い
It happened.
っちゃ った
Yeah.
うん
It's a naughty pussy.
エッチマンコやね
エ ッチマンコやね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Is it cold and comfortable?
寒くて気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Take your skin.
肌とって
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
It's already gone.
もういっちゃった
With your feet.
足で
I can make my pussy squeak.
おまんこキュッキュッキュってできる
It's easy to stop.
止まりやすいんだ
I can do that.
それできる
Your pussy feels so good.
おまんこめっちゃ気持ちいいよ
It's so pink.
すごいピンクだし
How do I relate to myself?
自分とはどうやって?
I wish I could use it on the back.
バックで使えたらいっちゃった
With a vibrator.
バイブで